EVELINA LARSSON

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Full-stack developer with an interest in front-end and a strong aptitude for styling now seeking a web development role in which I can grow with the product. London-based with 5 years advertising agency and team-building experience, I am highly organised, efficient and a fast learner with very good communication skills. Technical skills include Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and Adobe Creative Suite.

GET IN TOUCH

07942 883 223, aevelinalarsson@gmail.com

www.evelinalarsson.com

github.com/evelinalarsson

linkedin.com/in/evelina-larsson-ldn

RELEVANT TECH EXPERIENCE

Graduated in September 2019 as part of Le Wagon batch #287; a 9 week full-stack web development bootcamp in London.

My team and I dedicated the last two weeks to creating a product, and presented <u>126</u> at the Google Startup Campus. Our product was developed as an MVC application, helping the user decide what film to watch and food to order on a Friday night using a Netflix API and scraping the Deliveroo website.

<u>Limelite</u> is an Airbnb copycat where the user can search for or host unique film events (limited seeds). <u>My Cocktails</u> was my first MVC application, allowing the user to add, edit and delete cocktail recipes.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails
- HTML5, CSS3/SCSS, Bootstrap
- ES6 JavaScript
- Wireframes, prototyping, UI design
- Command line
- · Git, GitHub, technical workflow
- Content management systems
- QC and editing
- Adobe Creative Suite

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts - Publishing & English Lund University, Lund, Sweden, Sep 2005-Jun 2009

TRANSFERABLE SKILLS

- Excellent communication skills
- · Straight-forward and self-aware
- Hard-working, efficient
- Good team player and team builder
- Fast learner that enjoy challenges
- Leadership and managerial experience
- Good humoured, not easily stressed work well under pressure
- Self-motivated problem solver

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English (fluent)
- Swedish (native)
- Danish & Norwegian (conversational)

INTERESTS

Board games, puzzles, pub quizzes. Stencil printing. Creating the perfect pizza. Running in London, especially across the river. Camping & hiking - most recently I walked 75 miles alongside Hadrian's Wall from Carlisle to Newcastle. Flea markets and second hand shopping.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR ACCOUNT MANAGER

Hogarth Worldwide Ltd, London - Jan 2014-Jun 2019

- Client-facing technical account manager within a web development team, using Drupal to build websites for Nestlé Waters and Nespresso
- Project management responsibilities, including carrying out changes and building new pages in the CMS, internal QC, and meeting with creative agencies to discuss design, UI & UX
- Managed global campaigns within digital, TV & print production for Coca-Cola, Johnson & Johnson and Nespresso among others
- Sole responsibility for the Nordic Coca-Cola markets including scope of work, revenue, billing and client expectations
- Liaison between production departments to ensure information exchange remained unconvoluted
- Trouble-shooting role across various accounts to streamline production processes and internal workflows, foremost in connection with digital campaigns.

FREELANCING IN LONDON

Various roles, Oct 2012-Dec 2013

- Content Manager for a furniture start-up
- Content Writer for a Swedish online platform
- Sales Assistant securing accommodation for exchange students
- Prop Maker at Theatre Royal Stratford East.

ONLINE EDITOR

Kristianstad University, Kristianstad, Sweden - Jan-Jun 2012

- Extensive work with Episerver CMS recreating and transferring pages as part of a website update
- Creating, editing and maintaining content in English & Swedish
- Liaison between staff and management regarding updates and changes to the site.

ASSISTANT EDITOR

Folkuniversitetet Publishing House, Lund, Sweden - Mar 2009-Dec 2011

- · Editing, proof reading, translation and basic graphic design of language training material
- Content management on Episerver in connection with a website launch
- General administration, archiving and customer service.